Previously, Kim resorted to dirty tactics in
order to cause serious damage to Flash Mirage.
Isaac went to confront Kim.
But this caused tension between him and Mina.
After some convincing from Carson, Isaac decided to
compete using Mina's Sonic Blast, only to fail
once again because Kim sabotaged the race for
the sake of her own benefit.
Episode 12, The Test of Friendship
I see, so you're here too.
Oh, stop it.
I'm right here.
Why is this here?
Why do I have it?
I was worried you might get lost.
So I put it right inside your pocket.
Why are you here, Carson?
What do you want?
Shouldn't I be the one asking you that?
What are you doing here practicing so late
in the evening?
I've already seen Mina's data analysis of the
track.
Based on her analysis, more than half of
it are made out of slopes, and that's
tricky.
But as long as we can find a
way to get past the slopes, we should
stand a chance at winning the race tomorrow
morning.
Well, that's great to hear, coming from you.
You know, I was actually wondering, how could
you resist reporting Kim when she knocked you
off the track today?
It would have been very easy to do
that, you know.
You said it yourself, a real racer needs
to prove himself in the racetrack.
No matter what happens, even if the race
was played badly.
Besides, Mina would have to find out, too.
It would be heartbreaking, knowing that your best
friend betrayed your trust.
And I don't want that to happen.
Mina's my friend, too.
I can see how much you've grown as
time passes, Isaac.
You know what?
I think I want to help you do
something.
I'm keeping you company while you practice tonight.
Let's go around those slopes.
The first one who reaches the peak of
the slopes wins.
Three, two, one, go!
Why is it like this?
Somewhere in the middle of practice, I learned
that if I started riding between first and
second gear, I'll reach maximum power.
Don't you ever think that you can pull
a fast one on me.
I'm not letting you win.
You naive little kid.
What are you doing?
Right here.
Go, Storm Blade!
Wait, how could that be?
When driving on the slope, due to the
friction between the tires and the ground, if
you speed up all of a sudden, it's
going to cause damage to the motor.
But if you speed up while the car
is still in mid-air, you don't need
to worry about friction because there isn't any.
That way, the motor's going to be just
fine.
Okay, I gotta go.
What's going on?
Hey, I did it!
What are you doing there?
Listen, I think I found a way to
overcome the slope.
Huh.
Where have you been?
I've been trying to reach you, son.
Hey, Dad.
What can I do for you?
I found the component for the Flash Mirage
and sent them along with the assembly instruction.
You should be able to receive them very
soon.
Just sit tight, son.
It's on its way.
Also, I've learned some things regarding what you
told me the last time.
Actually, son, that clip is...
Hey, Kim!
I didn't expect you to ask me to
train with you this early.
I don't have a choice.
I'm the last one to attend the tournament,
remember?
How am I supposed to beat you if
I don't try hard enough to begin with?
It's all my fault.
It doesn't matter.
I've got a solution anyway.
My dad actually invented this chip.
As long as you put this chip on
it, you'll have much better control of your
car.
Hey, what are you doing?
I put one in my car.
Don't worry about it.
I want you to put one in yours
as well.
Let's see how it goes, okay?
All right, but...
Well, why don't we compare who gets a
better break between us?
A better break?
But, Carson, that clip...
Relax.
Don't worry, okay?
My dad says if the car is equipped
with that chip, it's going to have a
better reaction with the remote controller.
And the best way to test that is
through the brakes.
Don't worry, you'll see its results later.
The one who reaches the fountain first is
the winner.
Ready?
Okay, let's go!
That clip...
I was the one who put it on
his car.
I know it.
He's testing me right now.
If I step on the brakes now, he'll
know I played a dirty trick.
But if I don't, when Tai Chi Master
reaches the disturbance range, it's going to crash
eventually.
I know that chip was yours.
Aren't you afraid I might tell Mina the
truth?
My dad didn't give me that chip.
I picked it up at the mountain the
day Flash Mirage fell into an accident.
I also know that when a car is
equipped with that chip, the moment it goes
out of a certain range, the remote controller
won't be effective.
I think in all honesty, but you are
the only one who would think of putting
it in Isaac's car.
Does it really matter?
His car is already destroyed.
And besides, you're the last to qualify.
You're not the threat you used to be.
Mina considers you her best friend, doesn't she?
Why do you cheat on her like this,
Kim?
You should know this.
Whoever wins in Chengdu is going to get
double scores.
I've made every effort in order to win
the race in this area.
Does winning really matter that much to you?
With the skills you have, it shouldn't be
difficult for you to win a race fair
and square.
You don't understand.
You're from an honorable family, and you grew
up with a silver spoon in your mouth.
You'll never be able to understand how hard
it is for a girl to meet success
on the racetrack.
Mina once told me that you were very
kind and an extremely gentle soul.
But Kim, what could make you change like
this?
I don't need to explain myself.
I suggest you stay focused on tomorrow's race.
And remember, you're the last one to attend
the tournament.
You think you're going to win?
Well, Isaac and I know how to turn
the tables on you.
Mark my words, Kim, we're going to beat
you in a fair race.
See you tomorrow.
Huh?
What's up, Mina?
Why did you call me?
What's going on?
I wanted you to take a look at
this.
Ah!
Flash Mirage!
I was able to fix Flash Mirage using
the component that Uncle Liam sent over.
Go on, give it a try.
Okay!
Hmm.
It's much faster now.
And it's more responsive to the controls.
This is just the way I wanted it
to be when I first got it.
Finally.
I don't think I'll be able to ask
for anything more.
This is awesome.
Go on, try it on the slope.
Oh, Mina, it's high speed with three gears.
If I keep driving, it's going to be
underpowered in the middle of the slope.
I've reconfigured it.
Relax.
Everything's going to be just fine.
Don't worry.
Wait, Flash Mirage!
Just wait for it!
Isaac, do it now!
God vs.
Infinite Shift!
Incredible.
Thanks so much, Mina.
Well, just keep practicing, okay, Isaac?
I've got to help Kim re-equip her
car as well.
Re-equip?
Now that you know how to work around
the long slope and the track, I think
it's now time for me to help my
best friend.
She needs to run faster in the race,
and I'm going to help her.
Really?
Look, Isaac, I know you don't like her,
but what happened was really just an accident.
She didn't mean to do what she did.
I think you should forget about it.
I should go back.
Mina, wait!
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Are you trying to say she was trying
to sabotage your car?
Carson told me about it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to tell you.
But Mina, I don't want her to keep
cheating you the way that she's been doing.
Are you okay?
What's on your mind?
I'm fine.
I should go back.
Just keep training, okay?
Hey, Kim!
Oh, Mina.
Hey, you.
What's been going on?
What's up?
I happen to have Tai Chi Master with
me.
Could you re-equip it back at your
house?
Thanks, honey.
Remember when we were kids?
There was this one time when I spent
the night at your house.
Of course I do.
I remember that your dad promised to take
you to the movies that night.
Unfortunately, he didn't.
You were so angry with him and that's
why you stayed over.
That's right.
But that wasn't why I got so angry.
It's because he lied to me.
Could you answer this question for me?
When we met here in Chengdu, was that
by chance?
Of course.
Why would you ask me that, Mina?
I just want you to know something.
Whatever happened in the past, however difficult it
was, I'll always be here for you.
Well, if you really mean that, help me
re-equip my car.
If I
use the Ford gear to pass the curve
at this spot, will Storm Blade be able
to handle it?
Carson, I need your help right now.
327.1
Go on.
Is it right for me to re-equip
Kim's car?
She's your best friend, right?
I know, but Isaac told me everything.
I don't know what to do.
Answer my question.
Is she or isn't she your best friend?
Carson, if she really sees me as a
friend, then why did she lie to me
today?
If Kim really is your best friend, why
don't you go ask her this?
Why would she lie to you?
I don't know her personally, but I believe
someone you regard as your friend shouldn't be
as bad as they would seem to be.
My dad would always tell me that in
order to convince a rival, it's not enough
to know him.
More importantly, you have to do everything in
order to win him over.
And then that way, he'll realize his mistakes.
Whether or not you'll help Kim, it's your
decision.
I see.
Welcome to the Chendu Racetrack at the Race
10 World Super Remote Car Championship.
Today's race is going to last for a
total of 30 laps.
The champion of this leg will walk home
with his or her scores doubled.
After the results of the previous race, we
now have the terminal lineup of today's race.
First on the list is the only female
racer, Kim.
And coming in from other divisions, you've got
Carson and Isaac, who because of the accidents
during the qualifying race are now put at
the bottom positions on a temporary basis.
Whether or not they'll be able to do
a much better job today remains to be
seen.
The race will commence in a short while.
I don't think I can see Mina.
I wonder where she is.
Well, there's got to be something bothering her.
Let's just focus.
We need to do well.
Any minute now.
Ready.
On your mark.
Get set.
Go!
Let's do it.
Freely speed shifting!
Isaac and Carson performed freely speed shifting without
warming up their cars first.
It looks like they're out to regain their
former ranking.
However, the fact that they were able to
do that this early in the races shows
that they have a higher level skill which
may win them the race.
Will they be able to make it through
this time?
We'll find out.
Hang on to your seats, folks!
We've only run this track once, but we've
traded to mountains countless of times already and
spent countless of hours thinking of a way
to get past this.
Only this time, we're ready.
We're prepared for all situations.
Let's do it!
Flash Mirage!
Come on, Carson!
A fantastic run from Carson and Isaac.
They've just started overtaking everyone else and now
they're catching up to the top three.
They're coming in slowly but surely.
From the looks of it, conquering the tracks
of the Chengdu Lake isn't so hard after
all.
But can they actually finish on top?
They're really good at this whole racing game.
But I'm not going to let those two
catch up with me.
Is it just me?
What's wrong with her?
Blast it!
That car is in the way!
Isaac was so eager to overtake that he
found himself flying into the car right ahead
of Flash Mirage!
Whoa!
He's actually made it!
I hope nothing serious happens!
What are you doing?
Have you forgotten what happened to us the
last time, Isaac?
Don't overtake yet!
Got it!
The first lap is finally over!
Kim and Taichi Master are still in the
lead!
At first, Carson and Isaac who've been trying
to chase Kim were at the bottom, but
now they're in the middle of the ranking.
From this point onwards, it's anybody's game!
Brace yourselves, folks!
It looks like this is going to be
a very exciting race!
In the next episode, the tournament becomes more
intense.
Carson and Isaac are still bent on trying
to teach Kim a lesson that she will
never forget in her entire career as a
racer.
Could the friendship that Kim and Nina share
be nothing but a mere ruse?
In the next episode, Kim's secrets will slowly
be revealed and she is to learn her
most important lesson.
Will she be able to bear the burden?
Or will she lose herself and give up?